mysite.com 2004-12-07

# mySite.com Terms and Conditions- Low-cost email address - 1GB email storage - Block spam - Web & POP3 email access - Get your name as your email address

| |   

| Mega Web Services, Inc. ("Mega Web Services"), a United Online Company, provides various consumer Internet subscription services including Internet websites, web hosting services, domain registration, email services and other services (collectively, the Services) under multiple brands including mySite. Mega Web Services is committed to safeguarding your privacy online and created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting the online privacy of users of our services.

By using the Services you consent to our gathering, use and disclosure of your information, as described in this Privacy Statement, our Terms of Service and Acceptable Use Policy (collectively referred to as the Rules). This Privacy Statement may change from time to time and Mega Web Services will provide notice of changes as described in the Mega Web Services' Terms of Service.

Questions regarding this Statement should be directed to [privacy@support.mysite.com](mailto:privacy@support.mysite.com). Mega Web Services may also be contacted at: Attn: Legal Department - Privacy, Mega Web Services, Inc., c/o United Online, Inc., 75 9th Avenue, 4th Floor, New York, NY 10011.

This Privacy Statement explains the following: 

**

  1. What information does Mega Web Services gather?
  2. How does Mega Web Services gather information?
  3. How does Mega Web Services use the gathered information?
  4. With whom does Mega Web Services share information we gather?
  5. How may you access or update stored information about you?
  6. How does Mega Web Services protect your personal information?
  7. Use of Cookies; Email Pixels.

**  
---  
  
  1.  **What information does Mega Web Services gather?**

Mega Web Services collects personal information about you including, without limitation, personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, phone number and email address) and financial information (such as your credit card information). For some of our Services we may also ask other information about you such as your age or other demographic information. Mega Web Services may also collect your contact information and correspondence if you contact us by email or letter.

    *  **Information about you.** Mega Web Services collects personal information about you including, without limitation, personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, phone number and email address) and financial information (such as your credit card information). For some of our Services we may also ask other information about you such as your age or other demographic information. Mega Web Services may also collect your contact information and correspondence if you contact us by email or letter.
    *  **Information about your use of the Services.** Mega Web Services collects information about your use of the Services including, without limitation, data about your computer (such as operating system type, browser type, software installed on your computer) and your web browsing information (such as referring URL's as well as your IP address).
  
Back To Top
  2.  **How does Mega Web Services gather information?**

Mega Web Services gathers information that you submit on any Mega Web Services registration forms, surveys, questionnaires or other online forms. Mega Web Services gathers information about your use of the Services during such use, and you understand that you are not anonymous to us. Mega Web Services may also gather new information or update information from other sources including, for example, verifying and updating your address using third party services, using various methods to update your credit card expiration date or collecting information from our business partners.

Back To Top

  3.  **How does Mega Web Services use the gathered information?**

Mega Web Services uses your information to make your use of the Services more personalized and convenient. Mega Web Services uses your information to display or deliver materials, such as emails, surveys and content. Mega Web Services may use your information to target such materials so that they may be more relevant to you than materials that would be provided without the use of your information. Mega Web Services may use your information to make online transactions more convenient for you, such as pre-filling online forms that you may submit to us or, for some of our Services, this information may be pre-filled for third parties. Mega Web Services may provide your information to third parties as described below in Section 4.

    * Mega Web Services uses your information to conduct and provide market research and data analysis services.
    * Mega Web Services uses your information to provide, support and maintain the Services including, for example, to monitor and diagnose the Services, to provide technical support, to bill you for the Services and to contact you with respect to the Services or other Mega Web Services products or services.
    * You agree as a condition of your Service that Mega Web Services (and such third parties as authorized by Mega Web Services in compliance with this Privacy Statement) may furnish you, by email or other means selected by Mega Web Services, information prepared by Mega Web Services or by (or on behalf of) other entities including surveys, questionnaires, information, advertising and solicitations of new products, services, updates, account changes and technical services announcements, as well as other messages related to the Services. If no advertising is specified, you will still be required to receive advertisements and information related to Mega Web Services as well as advertising and information related to services that may be offered by United Online or its affiliated companies. You further acknowledge that any such advertisements and information are an inseparable part of the Service, and in order to opt-out of receipt you must terminate the Service.
Back To Top
  4.  **With whom does Mega Web Services share information we gather?**
    * Mega Web Services will not disclose your personally identifiable information to any third party, except if you have given us your consent for such disclosure or if the disclosure is described below. Mega Web Services may share your non-personally identifiable information with third parties.
    * Mega Web Services may share your personally identifiable information with third parties that provide services on behalf of Mega Web Services. Such third parties do not have the right to use your information for any purpose other than to provide the applicable service.
    * Mega Web Services may share your personally identifiable information with its affiliates.
    * If Mega Web Services sells, assigns or transfers the part of its business that provides a particular Service to you, your personally identifiable information may be sold, assigned or transferred as a part of such transaction.
    * Mega Web Services may disclose your personally identifiable information, any communications sent or received by you, and any other information that we may have about your account as follows: as may be required by law, regulation, rule or court order; pursuant to requests from governmental agencies or law enforcement authorities; as necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Rules; to operate the Services properly; or to protect Mega Web Services, our members or other third parties including, without limitation, other emergency situations.  

| |   
 **Third Party Sites and Co-Branded Services.**

Mega Web Services may advertise, promote, reference, recommend or provide links to third party sites, services and products. These third parties may have their own privacy policies, which may not comply with this Privacy Statement, even if the site, service or product is branded with Mega Web Services' logo or name. Mega Web Services IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF SUCH THIRD PARTIES OR ANY OTHER THIRD PARTIES. Mega Web Services recommends that you review the privacy policies of any such third parties.  
  
---|---  
Back To Top  

  5.  **How may you access or update stored Information about you?**

You may review and update your information stored as a part of your account in either the personal profile or billing information areas at any time. To access such information, please click on the "My Account" link or tab from the home page of your Service or by calling 1-877-503-0009.

Back To Top  

  6.  **How does Mega Web Services protect your personal information?**

All of your account information is password protected for your security. Your billing information is transmitted and displayed using industry-standard SSL encryption. While Mega Web Services believes that it has implemented reasonable security, Mega Web Services cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized third parties, such as hackers, from obtaining or accessing your information.

Back To Top  

  7.  **Use of Cookies; Email Pixels.**

Mega Web Services uses a feature of your Web browser called cookies to automate certain aspects of our Web site. Cookies are very small files that are stored on your computer and that enable us to recognize your computer each time you return to our site. By using cookies, Mega Web Services can keep track of your preferences, what you have already seen on our site and what you haven't, and any personalization you've done, without requiring you to enter a password every time you come back. Mega Web Services uses any information gathered using our cookies in compliance with this Privacy Statement.

Third parties, including advertisers with whom Mega Web Services may have a relationship, may also set cookies. Such third parties are responsible for placing and using such cookies and may collect information about you through such cookies; Mega Web Services does not have access to such cookies, control the use of such cookies nor control over the privacy policy of such parties.

We may use an email delivery and marketing company to send emails that you have agreed to receive. Pixel tags and cookies are used in those email messages and at our website to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site.

Back To Top
